{
    "subject": "resource/Inge_Morath",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Inge Morath",
    "human_readable": "The name of Inge Morath is Inge Morath.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9559974670410156,
            "question": "What is the name of Inge Morath?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.917131781578064,
            "question": "Is Inge Morath a person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.899080216884613,
            "question": "Who is Inge Morath?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7995796799659729,
            "question": "What can we infer about Inge Morath from her name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7918623685836792,
            "question": "Is there any other information available about Inge Morath besides her name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5640769004821777,
            "question": "Is there anything else we need to know to understand who Inge Morath is?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.560886561870575,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Inge Morath?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5245765447616577,
            "question": "What do we know about Inge Morath based on the given information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5231802463531494,
            "question": "If you were to write a brief biography of Inge Morath, what would you include based on the given information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4315442740917206,
            "question": "How would you describe Inge Morath using only the provided information?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Inge Morath is Inge Morath.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4939_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to write a brief biography of Inge Morath, what would you include based on the given information?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4939_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What do we know about Inge Morath based on the given information?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4939_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Inge Morath?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4939_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4939_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4939_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4939_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4939_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4939_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4939_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4939_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4939_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4939_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4939_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation result:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents confirm that the name \"Inge Morath\" indeed refers to a person named \"Inge Morath\". There are multiple mentions of her name throughout the documents, including as an artist, photographer, and the subject of various awards and foundations."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Inge Morath\" is the full name of the subject, and provide various details about her life and work as a photographer. Thus, the statement \"The name of Inge Morath is Inge Morath\" is supported by the information provided in the context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}